赞啊！赞啊！
Brava! Brava!
赞到不行啊！
Bravissima!
亲耐滴K 回见
Dear K, I G2G.
*I G2G I got to go 我得走了的缩写*
像Hans Solo样的向前冲吧
Go Hans Solo and all that.
*Hans Solo 星战著名角色*
我彷徨茫然哟 但是人生只有一次哟 对吧？
I don't know how to do this, but YOLO, right?
*YOLO You only live once 你只活一次的缩写，北美青少年爱用的口头禅 *
会再联系的哦 Tam酱
Holla at you soon, Tam-Tam."
小盆友简直神秘得就像...
Hmmm...kids they're as cryptic as...
黑暗派合同上的见证人签名？
...a witness signature on a Dark contract?
Tam酱是在跟随她的心
Tam-Tam's just following her heart.
我在想……
And I wonder...
现在我心上有个大洞
Now, I  have a big hole in mine.
没了记忆你还能知道你是谁吗？
Can you really know yourself without memory?
你还能知道你想要什么吗?
Can you know what you want?
我只希望她安全
I just hope she's safe.
当然我想滚床单滚它个天翻地覆
Well you want a whole lot of boom-boom.
天啊能和你吐槽真好
God, it is so good to finally dish.
我不知道没了你我该怎么办
I don't know what I would do without you.
我也是...
Me, too.
你没事吧？
Hey, are you okay?
来...
Come on...
你扶稳她了？
You got her?
恩 恩 坐下吧
Yeah, yeah. Sit down.
啊啊啊!
Ah-ah-ah!
你们这些傻x不帮忙的代价
Toll for being not-helping douche-balls!
水 亲
Water, honey.
你
You...
哇 她是俄罗斯人 真好
Whoa, she's Russian.Sweet!
肯子 能帮下忙吗？
Uh, a little help here, Kenz.
恩 不敢相信我找到你了！我找到你了！
Uh, "I can't believe I found you. I found you! I found you!"
主要就是在说她找到你了
She found you is the primary message.
我这辈子从没见过她诶
I've never seen her before in my life.
我来了 来了 来了 就像她告诉过我的那样
"I came. I came, I came,I came just like she told me to."
谁？谁告诉你来的
Who? Who told you to come?
你 你告诉我的
You. You did.
本作品片源来自互联网，仅供个人影视制作学习交流之用
任何组织和个人不得公开传播或用于任何商业盈利用途
挪威金毛的胡须最有爱了字幕组  r(st)q
英文字幕：来自互联网
翻译：Neffititi 骷髅头正宫_K
精校：Neffititi Joy 李夹碎
时间轴： Joy
发布：百度贴吧Tamsin后援群
资源下载请关注瓦尔基里字幕组官方微博
4x06 - Of All the Gin Joints
Bo 跟你说了 Ianka需要休息
Bo... I told you. Ianka needs to rest.
Trick 一个我见都没见过的妹子
Trick, some woman I don't know and never talked to
跟我说我叫她来找我
said I told her to come see me.
我不知道该不该相信她
I don't know if I believe her,
或者该相信什么
or what to believe anymore,
但是我得和她谈谈
but I need to talk to her.
行行好
Pretty please.
她需要休息 她是个Alkonost
She needs to heal. She's an Alkonost,
*Alkonost 俄罗斯传说中的一种半人半鸟的生物，歌声令人陶醉*
非常稀有柔弱的鸟人后代
a very rare and delicate descendant of bird people.
在寒冷中奔跑大概伤了她的声带
And running in the cold may have strained her vocal chords.
我猜唱歌是她的吸食方式？
Let me guess?Singing is how she feeds.
Alkonost的歌声能唤醒强大的记忆
The Alkonost's song evokes powerful memories.
等等 哪类记忆
Wait... What kind of memories?
好的坏的都有
Some good, some bad.
他们的歌声还能致命
Their songs can even take life.
不小心还会杀死自己
Including their own if they're not careful.
现在就让她休息吧
Just let her rest for now.
等丽沙异尼莉醒了 叫我一下
Well, when Liza Fae-nelli wakes up, let me know.
*Liza Minnelli 美国著名歌手*
要在54工作室你会很夺目
You would have killed at Studio 54.
就像我夺了
Just like I killed
那个把老娘的汽水弄错成汤力水的打杂的命一样
the busboy who served me tonic instead of soda.
你要干嘛
What do you want?
不过想来帮你搬家而已
Well, I thought I'd come over and help you move
但是显然我们现在当务之急
but clearly we have something more pressing to work on.
是提高你的待客技巧
Your hostessing skills ...
挫哦~迪士科女王
they suck ass, disco queen.
那个 我……我
Well, I-I...
没想到m女王会这样就
I didn't really expect The Morrigan just to...
带着啤酒和披撒出现
show up with...pizza and beer.
没有点za结尾的东西
Well, it's not a moving day party without some 'za,
还有我私人酿造仿的产品 还算什么搬家日
and a little something from my own personal microbrewery.
哦 哇
Oh, wow.
黑暗劣啤
"Dark Belch."
伦家那会有点红脖儿范儿
I was going through a redneck phase.
*redneck 粗鄙的乡下人*
不过产品可口 所以……
They were delicious, so...
也不后悔
no regrets.
还有我们要是真要合作的话
And please, if we're going to be working together,
就叫我Evony吧
call me Evony.
哦 哦 小心 小心
Oh, oh, careful! Careful.
哎呀 里面是啥呀
Jeez...What's in there?
是 恩  是我...
It's, um, my, uh...
星际迷航全套dvd收藏 没错
entire Star Trek DVD collection. Yeah.
企业号 航海家号 下一代 还有电影
Enterprise, Voyager, Next Generation. The movies.
*均为星际迷航剧集的系列名*
我的……
My...
漫展收藏小人
con collectible action figures.
哦 亲
Oh, honey...
我显然来得正是时候
I obviously came just in time.
浪子狼叔回归了
The prodigal wolf returns.
跑了两天两夜
Rode for two days straight.
对啊我也这么说的
Yeah, that's what I said.
Bo...
Dyson...
恩 看上去是坏消息的节奏啊
Well, that's not good news.
是Lauren
It's Lauren.
看起来她跟黑暗派混了
Looks like she has gone with the Dark.
恩 是吧
Oh, well, yeah.
你会笑的
You're gonna giggle.
真的 笑吧
Really, you are, but as it turns out...
我也变黑了
so did I.
啥?
What?
为啥？
Why?
我是被逼的行吗？
My hand was forced, okay?
被流浪者 Rainer还是什么的何弃疗弄的
By The Wanderer, or Rainer. Whoever the bastard is.
我们能改变的 我保证
We can fix this. I promise.
我知道该从哪开始
I think I know where we can start.
恩 我也知道
Yeah... so do I.
Bo你是黑暗派 我是光明派 我们不可以
Bo... you're Dark. I'm Light. We can't.
你明白吗？ 这是禁止的
Do you understand? It's forbidden.
很好
Good.
你喜欢吗?
Do you like that?
挺不同的
It's different.
我问的是 你喜欢吗?
I said...do you like that?
我会适应的
I'll learn.
是氧化水对声音好
Oxidated water is good for vocals.
还是没氧化的来着
Or, is it un-oxidated...
米诺陶的蛋蛋！
Balls of Minotaur!
*Minotaur 希腊神话中牛头人生的怪物 住在迷宫之中*
你俩在干嘛？
What's wrong with you two?
光明和黑暗不能深交！
Light and Dark can't fraternize!
Dyson!
我知道 我知道
I know. I know.
你俩都得警醒点
You both have to be smarter.
Una Mens无处不在
The Una Mens are everywhere.
那你出去的时候把门带上
So, close the door on your way out.
不 你俩停止乱搞
No. You get your brains out of each other's pants,
从我的酒窖里滚出去
and get out of my barrel room.
Ianka醒了
Ianka's awake.
别吓着她
Try not to aggravate her.
她很……
She's very...
娇嫩 我懂
...delicate. Yes. I know.
Ianka...
哦我的英雄 好高兴见到你
Oh! My hero.I'm so happy I found you!
我没以为真的会发生 可你确实在这
I did not think it would happen, but here you are.
我真的在这
And here I am.
我很高兴你没事 但
Well, I'm glad you're okay, but...
你到底在说什么 我从来没见过你啊
what are you talking about? I've never met you.
不是啊 但是...
No, but...
我给你唱歌后你来找我
you came to see me after I sang for you.
然后深深的触动了你
And it touched you so deeply.
你什么时候给我唱歌？在哪?
When did you sing for me?Where?
是在……那个……你让我保证了
It was at... the...You made me promise.
我让你保证什么?
What did I make you promise?
我要来这找到你
That I would come here and find you.
我说 不行 Bo 我做不到 那是不可能的
I said,"no, Bo, I can't, it's impossible."
但你坚持让我逃跑
But, you insisted I escape.
你给了我好大的启发
You gave me such inspiration.
我不明白 对不起
I don't understand. I'm sorry,
我不知道该说什么
I just don't know what to say.
那就听着
Just listen.
这特么……
What the hell...
是好的记忆吗？
It was a good memory?
恩 很……模糊
It was, um... vague.
很怪
And weird.
但是个线索 真的线索
But it was a clue, a real clue.
Ianka 拜托了 再唱点什么
Please, Ianka, sing more.
不 我们说好了的
No. We shook on it.
我给你唱歌
I sing for you
你给我这世界上我最想要的东西
and you get me what I want most in the world.
那是?
Which is?
自由
Freedom.
Ianka你不能拿我的记忆做人质诶
Ianka, you can't hold my memories hostage.
不我没有你的记忆
No, I do not have your memories.
你自己才拥有你的记忆
Only you have your memories!
我只有开启它们的钥匙
I only have the key to unlock them.
那你应该把钥匙给我
You should probably give me this key.
哦...大家都谈论淫妖
Oh...People talk about the Succubus,
说你是不同的
and they say you are different,
但是你和其他人也半斤八两
but you are just like the others.
你答应了给我翅膀
You promise me my wings
然后你拔了我的羽毛就为了听我唱歌
and then you pluck my feathers so you can hear me sing.
对不起
I'm sorry.
最近我觉得很茫然
Lately, I've just been feeling so lost.
等等 其他人是谁?
Wait... What others?
我给一个富有的布拉克唱歌
I sing for a wealthy and powerful Buraq.
*Buraq 古兰经中记载的一种飞马 供先知骑乘*
只能给他唱
Him, and only him.
可我好饿 我不能吸食
But I am starving. I cannot feed.
要是我能给听众唱歌
If only I could sing for an audience.
要是我能唱我著名的咏叹调
If only I could sing my Famous Aria.
我还是更喜欢黑眼豆豆一点
Guess I'm more of a Black Eyed Peas kind of girl.
*Black Eyed Peas 美国著名嘻哈乐队*
不遗憾过往 也不畏惧将来
"Ni Regrette Du Pass? Ni Perdu De  L'Avenir."
啊 啥意思?
Hm? It means,
不遗憾过往 也不畏惧将来
"Neither regret the past nor fear the future."
哦 很优美
Well, it's beautiful.
可对我来说一无是处
But, it doesn't mean anything to me.
你 你说...你不会记得
You, you said...you would not remember.
拜托 看看你的刀
Please, uh, look in your knife.
刀柄...
The handle...
Ianka 你会给我唱歌 而我会让你自由
"Ianka, you will sing for me, and I will bring you freedom."
这是我的笔迹
That's my handwriting.
Ianka
Ianka!
哦不
Oh, no.
Bo 求求你帮我 他来了
Please, Bo, help me. It's him.
他是谁
Who him?
Ianka! Ianka!
这地方的主人是谁？
Who is the owner of this establishment?!
我的Ianka在哪？可怜的东西!
Where is my Ianka? The poor thing!
嘿 她才不是物品 亲
Hey! She's not a thing, pal.
没人拥有她
And nobody owns her.
这不对
That is not true.
美丽的Ianka归我家族所有已经很多年了
The beautiful Ianka has been in my family for centuries.
恩 一万多年前
Yeah, well, four score and a bunch of years ago,
林肯倒下了
Lincoln threw down
*渡渡鸟 一种已绝种的鸟类*
奴隶制随渡渡鸟一去不返
and slavery went the way of the Dodo.
让她走吧
So, let her go.
你这可笑的孩子
Surely, you jest.
把她给我 马上
Bring her to me. Now.
对不起哦
Sorry.
Ianka十分钟前就走了
Ianka left ten minutes ago.
不 她没有
No, she didn't.
她在这里
She's here.
你给她弄了个GPS?
You put a GPS on her?
她成什么了? 耳朵里植入芯片的狗吗?
What is she? A dog with a chip in her ear?
别搞笑了
Don't be ridiculous.
装置在她的项链里
The device is in her necklace.
那我就得把项链扯下来
Then I'll rip it off her.
你试试
Try it.
只会缠得更紧
And you'll only tighten it around her throat.
她只想唱著名的咏叹调
All she wants is to sing the Famous Aria.
你就答应她吧
And all I ask is that you allow it.
著名的咏叹调
The Famous Aria...
让普通人听真是浪费
wasted on the masses.
你这是在骂我呢
Now, you're just insulting me.
大家谈论你的大方和善良
People speak of your generosity.Your benevolence.
在下不才
Well, I am both.
要是大家发现你从Ianka身上剥夺了这两样
Well, when the public finds out that you deprived them
他们就会看清你的真面目
of a performance by Ianka,they'll see who you truly are.
等等 我只是还没决定好
Wait now... I simply hadn't made up my mind.
好吧...我同意
Hmm... I will allow it.
不过得有个包间
But, I need a private room, a bottle
一瓶25年陈的Scapa麦芽威士忌
of Scapa 25 single malt,
还要有个……不黏糊糊的座位
and a place to sit that's not so... sticky.
不黏糊糊是可以的
I can do less sticky.
个人日记 职业日记
The personal and professional journals
马约 爱因斯坦 和居里夫人的？
of Charles Mayo, Albert Einstein,and Marie Curie?
怎么可能？
How?
居里夫人就是个傻x
Marie turned out to be a real axe wound
我开玩笑偷了她的日记
so I stole her diary as a joke.
*Jimmy Hoffa 美国工会领袖 神秘失踪*
马约的是从Jimmy Hoffa那扒出来的
Mayo's I dug up from under Jimmy Hoffa and
爱因斯坦的？
Einstein's?
*Garage sale 在自家车库门口摆摊出售不要的东西*
旧物出售买来的
Picked that up at a garage sale.
你还去旧物出售呢？
You go to garage sales?
恩恩
Mm-hmm.
你都不知道人类为了几块钱啥都能卖
You wouldn't believe the shit that humans will sell for a few sawbucks.
*斯特拉迪瓦里 著名小提琴制造师*
我的梵高 斯特拉迪瓦里小提琴
My Van Gogh, my Stradivarius
两颗法贝热彩蛋
two Faberge eggs.
*法贝热彩蛋 为沙皇专门制作的彩蛋 非常精美*
法贝热本人要知道了准得气死
Gustav Faberge would lose his shit if he knew.
他们都是异种？
They were Fae?
这些日记都是异种写的？
Are all these journals from the Fae?
档案里还有很多很多
There's hundreds more in the archives.
噢 1830年七月三十日
Oh..."July 30, 1830...
病人 O’Connor 曾经成功的
Patient O'Connor, who was previously and successfully
注射了结核杆菌
injected with tuberculosis bacilli
昨晚病情忽然加重去世
took a turn last night and died.
这个医生在做人体实验啊
This doctor was experimenting on humans.
真是寻常的黑暗派的麻木不仁
That's typical Dark Fae callousness.
噢 傲慢的人类
Oh, the hubris of your kind.
他可不是什么异种
That doctor was not Fae.
好吧
Oh, well...
虽然我对自己的职业很骄傲
although I am very proud of my profession,
可我也没总是赞同前辈的做法
I haven't always agreed with the methods of my forefathers.
为什么?
Why not?
抗凝剂  流感疫苗  基础解剖
Anticoagulants, flu vaccines,basic anatomy.
人类的医药治疗还是
You know, medicine and treatment meant for
在人类身上研究来得好
humans is best researched on humans.
哇
Wow.
哇 我是说  你的理论还能再过时点吗?
Wow. I mean, could your theories be any more outdated?
现在我们都用上电脑研究疾病寻找药物了
We actually use computers now to navigate diseases
我们可以培育器官 组织样品
and help find cures. We can grow organs, tissue samples...
噢 噢 折个中
Oh, oh, compromise.
克隆个谁然后在他身上试验吧
We can clone somebody and experiment on them.
不 那太恶心了
No. It's disgusting.
我不会做的 你也不能强迫我
I won't do it and you can't make me.
Lauren 冷静 喝点酒
Lauren, calm down.Have a drink.
听着 你不用做你不想做的事
Look, you don't have to do anything that you don't want to.
但是 我想让你没有拘束
But, I want you to feel free.
哦好吧  可是道德呢？伦理呢？
Oh, okay, and morals? Ethics?
被高估了
Overrated.
但是要是对你来说很重要
But, if they're important to you,
我会尊重你的意见
I can respect that.
要是我同意和黑暗异种一起工作
If I agree to work with the Dark Fae,
那得按我的条款
it will have to be on my own terms.
好吧 行
Fine. Right.
以女童军的荣誉起誓
Scouts honour.
Kenzi  你得离开这
Kenzi, you need to get out of here.
Alkonost的歌声可能会伤到人类
An Alkonost's song can hurt humans.
你丫都在我耳朵边放了四年碾压神经
After nearly four years of your nerve-shredding
糊我一脸的歌了...
fiddle-dee-pluck-me-holy-cloveers-shoot-me-in-face music...
我想我没事的
I think I can handle it.
Kenzi你真的得走了
Kenzi... you really should go
我哪也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
真不好意思 我可是你的头号粉丝
I am so sorry,but I am your biggest fan.
噢！哦！天啊 你怎么样？
Oh!!! Ah! Ah! Oh, my God!How are you?
你怎么样？
How are you?
挺好的
I'm good!
你在这干嘛呢
What are you doing here?
好吧她又有名 又漂亮 又是俄罗斯人
So, she's famous and beautiful and Russian.
又讨厌 又空虚 又清高
She's also obnoxious and vain and stuck up...
你知道俄语里的歌手其实是小姐的意思的吗
And did you know that "singer" in russian actually means "whore?"
其实并不是
Except it doesn't...
你在听我说话吗
Are you listening to me?
肯子 她是钥匙
She is the key, Kenz.
能开启我的记忆 让我找到Rainer
To my memories, to finding Rainer,
谁知道还有什么
and who knows what else.
火车...我在火车上
A train... I'm on a train.
我几乎能看到他的脸了...
I can almost see his face...
不好意思打扰了亲们
So sorry for the interruption, folks,
但这位唱歌的大小姐身上可绑了炸弹
but this prized songstress of yours is wired to blow.
你们要是不按我说的做
If you don't do exactly as I say,
小鸟就会爆炸
the little bird goes kaboom.
看来是我们粉墨登场的时候了
Looks like it's our turn to take centre stage.
有人惹了不该惹的歌手
Somebody just crossed the wrong diva.
要是这的谁想死
If anyone here has a death wish,
就来制止我吧
by all means try and stop me.
Ianka的项链  那些水晶
It's Ianka's necklace, the crystals.
一个粉在里面装了GPS 其他的
One music fan puts a GPS in it and the other...
都装着炸药  没错
Programs it to explode.Correct.
你是谁 你想干嘛
Who are you and what do you want?
他是Marcus 玛雅蝙蝠战士Camazotz
He is Marcus, a Camazotz Mayan Bat Warrior.
*Camazotz 玛雅神话中的蝙蝠神 与死亡 牺牲 黑夜联系紧密*
他是为了Ianka来的
And he's come for Ianka.
就像你多年前一样
Just like you did all those years ago.
我得到她了 对吧?
And I got her, didn't I?
恩然后我又把她偷回来了
Uh huh... And I stole her back.
你要再干一仗吗
Do you wish to start another war?!
你才想干仗
It is you who wishes to fight.
对Camazotz来说
In all Camazotz,
Ianka唤醒那些赢了的战争
Ianka evokes memories of battles waged and won.
鼓舞他们的军队的士气
It bolsters their armies.
我接受你的挑衅
And I say yes to your provocation.
再对我们布拉克说一个字 我们就要血洗你
One word to my fellow Buraqians, and we shall rain fire on you!
别！
No!
任何动荡都会引起
Unrest of any kind will bring unwanted attention
Una Mens不必要的注意
from the Una Mens.
著名的咏叹调把她变虚弱了
- The Famous Aria has weakened her.
这够了
This is too much.
移动一个虚弱的Alkonost可是会要了她的命
Moving an Alkonost when she is weak is a death sentence.
你要她活着吗？那你得让她休息  Marcus
You want Ianka alive? You need to let her rest, Marcus.
这会让她恢复些力气
This will help her regain her strength.
是啊 给我们点机会看看那些水晶
Yeah, and give us a chance to look at those crystals.
那不是水晶 那是亚特兰帝斯石英
They're not crystals. They're Atlantean Quartz.
以前被认为会引发火山爆发
Once thought to ignite volcanic eruptions.
哦 Marcus说的卡砰 原来是真的
Oh. When Marcus said kaboom, he really meant it.
那我们怎么才能让它停止
So, how do we stop this?
石英要被冷冻
The Quartz needs to be frozen.
可只有液态火山氩才有用
But only liquid volcanic argon will do the trick.
没事 我会让Kenzi去地道
No biggie, I'll send Kenzi to the tunnels.
去哪？
To where?
液态火山氩商店
The liquid volcanic argon store.
再来 再来
- Okay, do it again!
好好好
Okay, okay, okay!
医生的日志  星际年4365.3 和Evony坐在沙发上
Doctor's log, stardate 4365.3, sitting on couch with Evony,
又称m女王 与人类惊人的相似
AKA The Morrigan, who seems suspiciously human.
为什么？因为我有感情？
Why? Because I have feelings?
我不知道 我通常不会把你和
Oh, I don't know.Empathy and compassion are two
同情心 换位思考这种东西联系起来
words I would not usually associate with you.
天啊我觉得我有点醉了 我才喝了一瓶
My God, I think I'm tipsy. I've had one beer.
百分之二十五的酒精？真的假的？
Twenty-five percent alcohol?! Are you kidding me??
*普通啤酒酒精含量一般在10%以下*
恩哼
Ahem.
嗨 平行宇宙的Lauren
Hi! Alternate reality Lauren.
我要跟Lauren的真身说话
I'd like to talk to the real Lauren,
拜托叫她来 谢谢
so please go get her.Thank you.
劣啤？
Belch?
你气色变好了点
Well, you're getting your colour back.
能见到个熟脸真好
Oh, it's so good to see a face from the past.
你的脸
Your face.
还记得以前晚上我们在露天剧场恶作剧
Remember the pranks we used to play in the amphitheatre after
在靠近那个
dark? In the, ... near the…
你怎么称呼它？太空石头？
how did you call it?Space rock?
音速陨石
Sonic meteorite.
恩
Hmm.
没错
Yeah.
我会打电话 比比比比
I would dial the tone...beep, boop, bap!
你记得你会问什么吗
Remember what you would ask?
啊对你的冰箱能用吗
Ah, yes.Is your refrigerator on?
然后他们说对 然后我说那你最好去抓住它
And they say yes, and I say, "then you better go and catch it."
你老让笑话冷场
You mess the joke up every time.
哦 你出丑了 不过...你让我笑了
Oh, you make fun.But... you make me smile.
谢谢你 来看我
Oh... thank you. For the visit.
但是 我得躺下来
- But, I must lie down.
当然了
Of course.
好 再给我解释一遍
Okay, explain this to me again.
你和Bo需要液态氩
You and Bo need liquid argon
加到你们自制的梅乐酒桶里
to add to the barrels of your homemade merlot
* merlot：红葡萄酒的一种品种*
为了防止氧化
in order to avoid oxidation?
没错 不用担心什么
Yup! Yeah, nothing to worry about.
这是我们的新玩意儿 你懂的啦  传统家酿美酒
It's just our new thing.You know, a good old home hooch.
看来你也有个新玩意儿
Looks like you got something new, too.
你们这是要同居的节奏？
You guys, like, moving in together?
不我们就是聊聊  而且因为这地方
No, we're just talking,and since this place
属于光明派 Evony帮我在城里找了一个新的loft公寓
belongs to the Light, Evony helped me find a great new loft in the city.
Evony 恩 好奇怪
Evony. Hm.Wow. Weird.
这闻起来可不像果珍
This doesn't smell like Kool Aid.
Bo怎么样了
How's Bo?
挺好
Good.
你懂 黑烟和那个石像鬼
You know, uh, black smoke and gargoyles
*Gargoyles:石头雕刻的滴水嘴兽，被用来警告人们世界末日将近，他们要尽多去教堂。*
和透明的亚特兰帝斯石英 和往常一样
crystal clear Atlantean Quartz, the usual.
但是她 她很想念你 我们也是
But, she, uh...she misses you. We all do.
等等 你刚说了透明的亚特兰帝斯石英？
Wait...did you say clear Atlantean Quartz?
退后
Stay back.
你不想伤害Ianka
You don't really want to harm Ianka.
是吗
Do you?
我做我自己想做的事
I want what I want.
也许你告诉我们那是什么  我们可以帮你
Well, maybe if you tell us what that is, we can help you out.
我不能告诉你  但是要是需要我炸飞Bamber的小鸟
I can't say, but achieving it means blowing up Bamber's prize bird...
那没错 我会伤害她
Then yes, I will harm her.
你懂的 劫持一酒吧的人质可是很弱鸡的举动
'Ya know, it's a weak man who keeps a bar full of innocent hostages.
你快点离开
You leave.
不要以你的生命为代价
Not on your life.
也不要以她的生命为代价
And especially not on hers.
现在
Now.
小男人和他们的小玩具们
Little men and their little toys.
我会在楼上 我不会让你有事的
I'll be upstairs. I won't let anything happen to you.
完成任务
Mission accomplished?
答应你的Bamber的发射机
Bamber's transmitter, as promised.
这东西能用吗?
Will it work?
妥妥的
Like a charm.
现在是接收器了
You are now looking at a receiver,
我为秘密情报局工作的一点好处
compliments of my days with the SIS.
*SIS 英国情报机构 又称MI6*
等等 你必须
Please, you must...
我不行 而且你会
I can't.And you will be...
Bamber 马上就来了...
Bamber will come after...
说出他的名字
speak his name.
有人在偷听
Someone's listening to us.
结束了
It's over.
不要这么说!
Don't say that!
对不起   Ianka
I'm sorry, Ianka.
不 求求你 Marcus 不要
Please, Marcus, no!
那是引爆装置 他按下去了
The detonator.He pressed it.
所有人趴下!
Everybody get down!
Bo 发生什么了 我错过什么了吗?
Bo, what's happening? What did I miss?
我必须告诉你一件事
Oh, and I have to tell you something.
石英没有引爆
The Quartz didn't detonate.
当然没有了 里面没有火了
Of course not. There's no fire in it anymore.
它是死的 没用了 假货
It's dead, done, a fake.
*Mayan apocalypse：玛雅人的日历在2012年停止，被深信是世界末日的预言*
你知道的 就跟玛雅人的世界末日论一样
You know, like the Mayan apocalypse.
艾马 太坑爹了 拜托...
God, what a rip that was. Come on...
好吧  项链的透明度 证明了它的不挥发性
Oh, okay.The transparency of the necklace proves it's involatility.
你现在才告诉我？
Now you're telling me?
医森上身
Channeling Dr. Lauren.
哦对 她怎么样了
Oh, yeah, right. How is she?
好 很好 总的来说...
Good! Good, yeah, you know, in a general, uh...
顺便问问你你看见Hale了吗?
alone sense. BTdubs, have you seen Hale?
小黑？看到了
Hale? Yeah.
他……大概在附近吧
He's...you know, around. Probably.
我想我得去找他
I think I'm going to go find him.
好
Okay.
Ianka走了 和Marcus一起
Ianka's gone. Her and Marcus.
他把她从我们眼皮子底下顺走了
He took her right from under our noses.
但是为什么现在才溜走?
But why now?
他们在帘子下干嘛
And what were they doing behind that curtain?
看起来像翠地鸟和傻大猫把笼子打翻了
Looks like Tweety and Sylvester have flown the coop.
*Tweety and Sylvester 著名动画 主角为小黄鸟和大黑猫*
那么告诉我 她是不是也有份？
So, tell me, was she in on this?
我母鸡
I don't know.
听着 她有我想要的答案 所以
Look, she has the answers that I need, so somebody
你们谁最好告诉我 小子 你就是那颗幸运星
better start talking, and lucky boy, that's going to be you.
当我的家人把 Ianka从Marcus那里偷走
When my family stole Ianka back from Marcus...
我的女歌者不再如从前了
my songstress was not the same.
她的心里有一道新的光芒
There was a new light in her.
而我们之间出现了新的距离
And a new distance between us.
Ianka从来不怕Marcus 从来没有
Ianka was never afraid of Marcus. Not once.
他们是一伙的吗?
Are they partners?
Marcus很激进 对所有的布拉克
Marcus is a radical, bent on hatred for all
充满了仇恨 我就知道这些了
Buraqians. That is all I know.
走吧
Now leave.
Bo 在这里
Bo! Over here.
看这个
Check it out...
Trick曾经把他的万用发射器藏在这 用这个的话
This is where Trick used to hide his rare Omni transmitter. With it,
Marcus可以从任何地方  发射任何东西
Marcus could broadcast anything, from anywhere.
你还会修车
You fix cars, too?
你以为谁换了你的火花塞？
Who do you think's been changing your spark plugs?
我就爱你这一面  爱
I love this side of you. Love...
爱
Love.
什么?
What?
Dyson 他们相爱了
Dyson, they're in love!
Bamber就是想说这点
That's what Bamber was trying to say.
Marcus和Ianka相爱了
Marcus and Ianka are in love.
但是 那和发射器有什么关系?
But, what's that got to do with the transmitter?
你觉得Bamber家会让他们在一起吗?
You think the Bambers would ever let them be together?
要是Bamber家族消失了
But, if there were no Bambers...
Ianka可以唱死亡颂诗
Ianka can sing death notes.
她和Marcus  他们要把那些人全杀光
She and Marcus... they're going to kill them all.
但是在哪里?
But where?
我偷听到Hale提到某种在Bambe的地盘声波石阵
I overheard Hale mention some kind of sonic stonework on Bamber's estate.
快 我们得赶紧
Come on, let's go.
那可有一群布拉克呢
There's dozens of Buraqians.
我们得去警告他们
We have to warn them all in person.
快去吧  小狼
Go get 'em, Wolfy.
Bo Hale不见了 消失了
Bo! Hale is gone! Missing.
噢...什么?
Oh... what?
这些鸟女 她们可以用声音伤害异种
These bird women, they could hurt Fae with their voices.
哪种程度的伤害 致残  致死吗?
Hurt how? Bad hurt? Dead hurt?
我和你一起去
I'm coming with.
不 太危险了
No. It's too dangerous.
没有商量的余地
This is not a discussion!
Hale不见了 我还没有告诉他我
Hale's gone and I haven't even told him that I...
我懂的 来吧 我们去好好干上一场架
I know. Come on, let's go kick some serious ass.
Ianka 停下来
Ianka, stop!
我们已经告诉了布拉克们你要唱死亡颂诗
The Buraqians has been warned of your death note as we speak.
对 我也是这意思
Yeah! What she said!
死亡颂诗 不 我不会唱这种东西
Death note? No. I am singing no such thing.
Marcus和我只想在一起
Marcus and I only want to be together.
那发射器是用来干嘛的
And the transmitter?
告诉他的家人我们有多相爱  对吧亲爱的?
To tell his family about our love. Right, my darling?
Ianka 有些事情比爱更重要
Ianka...some things are bigger than love.
不 你想要我
No... you want me to...
我不会杀 Bamber家族的
I will not kill the Bambers.
我可不是在询问
I'm not asking.
啊 求你了  Marcus停下来
Ah! Please, Marcus, stop!
Bo  Bo 帮忙啊
Bo, Bo, help...
不 不是那样
No, not like that!
Bo让我来结束他
Bo, let me finish him.
我要是听见
I hear anything other
任何不是死亡颂诗的东西  我就突突你们所有人
than the death note, this gun mows you all down.
所有人离开这里  我要和Marcus谈谈
Everybody get out of here! Marcus and I need to talk.
Kenz离开这里
Kenz, leave!
我不会走的 我来这里救你的
I'm not leaving! I came here to rescue you!
大家快走
Guys, go!
这是什么 灵魂火车?
What is this?Soul Train?
Marcus 求你别这样
Marcus, please stop all this.
这不是你  这样的愤怒 丑陋的仇恨
This isn't you.This anger, this ugly hate...
唱死亡之音
Sing the death note.
你爱我
You love me.
快唱吧 贱人
Just sing already, you bitch.
停止！
Stop!
不...
No...
哦金属教母啊好痛痛啊
Oh, Mother of Metallica, this hurts!
Hale 把你爱的妹子拖出去
Hale, get the woman you love out of here.
拜托!
Please!
不，别
No, please!
噢  Ianka
Oh, Ianka...
Ianka...求你...
Ianka... please...
Ianka  Ianka 你成功了
Ianka, Ianka, you did it.
Marcus他  他死了
Marcus, he's...he's gone.
听着 我会搞定Bamber的
Look, I will take care of Bamber.
你会自由的 我保证  来  你能走吗?
You will be free, I promise. Come on, can you walk?
噢 不 亲爱你
Ugh! No, dear...
你不明白
you do not understand.
我在虚弱的时候杀了人
I took life in a weakened state.
我再不能……
I am... no more.
你会……
You're going to...
Ianka拜托你告诉我你没牺牲你自己
Oh, Ianka, please tell me  you didn't sacrifice yourself.
总会有人想拥有我
Someone would have  always tried to own me.
这是我族人的宿命
It is the fate of my people.
大家都无所谓 可我不行
Most do not mind, but I do.
我是唯一一个能阻止的人
I was the only one who could stop it.
我要给Trick打电话 一定有什么
I'm gonna call Trick. There's gotta be
我们能做的  药水 或者……
something that we can do,some kind of potion, or...
被囚禁时我听说了不结盟的淫妖的事
In captivity, I heard stories about the unaligned Succubus...
你让我相信我能自由
You are what made me believe I could be free.
可我再不是不结盟的了
But I'm not unaligned anymore.
你的心会成为你所追寻的东西
Your heart is what you want it to be.
现在 我的心自由了
Right now, my heart is free.
为了你  你所期待的
For you...as you wished.
哦不Ianka别
Oh, no... Ianka, no.
啊  尼玛的高音宿醉
Ugh...Holy high-pitched hangover.
哇哇哇 别这么快 好了好了
Whoa, whoa, not so fast.There you are.
啊 发生了啥事  Bo呢?
Ugh. Oh...What happened? Where's Bo?
她没事 Ianka唱了死亡之音  Marcus挂了
She'll be fine. Ianka sung a death note. Marcus is dead.
哦 真有她的
Oh.Good for her.
她也会死的
It would have killed her, too.
哦 Hale...对不起
Oh, Hale... I'm so sorry.
她终于自由了
She's finally free.
是啊
Yeah.
然后你   你终于在这了
And you...you're finally here.
我一直都在
I've... always been here.
真心话  Ianka的死亡之音伤到你了吗?
Now truth, Ianka's death note, did it hurt you?
没
No.
你要敢跟俄罗斯恶眼撒谎
Hey, you lie to the Russian stink eye,
可是要烂丁丁的
and bad things will happen to your junk.
对我来说可是好可惜
Which would now be a particular bummer for me.
俄罗斯恶眼……挺强的
This Russian stink eye...it's pretty intense.
习惯吧
You'll get used to it.
哦别 我不行
Oh, no... no, please...I can't do this.
Bo?
别告诉我你不以面具示人
Don't tell me you don't wear a mask to protect yourself
你的面具可是冷漠得要命
Hm. Yours is especially...chilling.
高处不胜寒啊 你被变态和杀手环绕
The higher you climb,the more you realize that you're surrounded by sycophants and assassins.
你好狗血
You're so dramatic.
不  我是狗血中的奇葩 亲
No, I am realistic in a dramatic world, honey.
你会知道的
You'll see.
他们也会找上你的
You'll get your share of sycophants and assassins too.
是吗 那你是哪种?
Oh yeah?Which one are you?
现在？你可以叫我朋友
For now?You can call me a friend.
这是黑暗科学医学实验中心的钥匙
This is the key to the dark science  medical and testing facilities.
你的 畅通无阻
It's yours. Full access.
我不会签什么合同的
I won't sign anything.
谁让你签了
I'm not asking.
你是个聪明的女人 走起
You are a brilliant woman.Own it girlfriend.
我不会相信你
I'll never trust you.
你要相信了才怪呢
I wouldn't respect you if you did.
但是记住你看到了我吃披撒的样子
But do remember,I let you see me eat pizza.
你以为那是人人都能看的？
You think I just let any schmo do that?
你新公寓的钥匙
Here are the keys to your new condo.
要是还需要什么就打给我
Call me if you need anything else.
真是挺……怎么说来着?
This was ah...what do they call it?
愉快 对吧？
Fun. Right?
Evony
Evony.
披撒是我们的秘密
Pizza's our secret.
我想这大概会是一个
I think this might be the beginning of a beautiful...
美好的开始
something.
还是不信任你
Still don't trust you.
不用你信任Lewis医生
You don't have to, Dr. Lewis.
你是黑暗队了
You are Team Dark now.
我尝出来了
I can taste it.
白白了 亲
Ta, darling.
为了开始干杯
To... the beginning.
Bo 看着我
Bo... look at me.
Bo 拜托 看着我
Bo... please, look at me.
别对我挥来喝去！
Don't tell me what to do!
对不起
I'm sorry.
对不起 我只是
I'm sorry, I'm just uh...
愤怒  没事的
Angry. It's okay.
没人拥有你
No one owns you.
你不会像Ianka一样的
You're not going to be like Ianka.
不 我会像Marcus一样
No. I'll become like Marcus.
在自己无尽的愤怒中痛苦的窒息 除了复仇什么都不想
Bitter, choking on my bottomless rage, thinking of nothing but revenge.
Ianka为了自由而死 Dyson
Ianka died to be free, Dyson.
就那么一小会
For just a few moments.
你启发了她
And you inspired her to do that.
不 不是我 是另一个Bo
No, not me. Another Bo.
我都不认识她
One that I don't even know.
不管她是谁  她没在虚无里睡了一个月
Whoever that Bo was, she didn't spend a month asleep in limbo.
她在火车上 有计划
She was on a train, hatching a plan.
给未来的自己准备线索
Sending herself clues in the future.
她...
She...
我……加入了黑暗
I... joined the dark.
自愿的
Willingly.
那我想你肯定有你的理由
Then I'm sure you had good reason.
再说了  黑暗 光明 不过是标签
Besides, dark... light...these are just labels.
又不定义我们
They do not define us.
看来我不是唯一变了的人
Looks like I'm not the only one who's changed.
你受伤了
You're hurt.
我不知道 可我很痛苦
I don't know.But I am hurting.
他给我做了记号
He marked me.
谁?
Who?
流浪者  雨人
The Wanderer. Rainer.
他可能是我爸
He might be my father.
这尼玛是啥？
What the hell is this?!
地下巡逻队？
Mole patrol?
法典被违犯了
The codex of laws has been infringed upon.
你的规则在老娘这行不通
Your rules don't apply to me.
不是你 他
Not you. Him.
Dyson 别！
Dyson, no!